Register of the John G. Veneman papers, 1959-1981
Hoover Institution Archives
John G. Veneman papers
1959-1981
82059
Hoover Institution Archives
26 manuscript boxes, 6 envelopes, 22 sound cassettes (13.6 linear feet)
Correspondence, speeches, memoranda, reports, clippings, sound recordings, and photographs relating to domestic political issues in the United States, especially welfare and social policy, and to national and California state politics.
Veneman, John G., 1925-1982
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1982.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Biographical Note
1925 October 31 Born, Corcoran, California
1944 Graduated from Arizona State College Served with United States Naval Reserve
1944-1945 Attended the University of Texas
1947 June 22 Married Nita D. Bomberger
1956 Elected to the Empire School District Board
1959-1962 Supervisor, Stanislaus County, California
1960 Chairman, Stanislaus County Board of Supervisors
1962-1969 Member, California State Assembly
1964-1969 Member, California Social Welfare Board
1969-1973 Under Secretary, Department of Health, Education and Welfare, Washington, D.C.
1972 Conducted a course on welfare programs, New School of Social Research, New York City, New York
1973 Lecturer, Eagleton Institute of Politics, Rutgers University
1973- President, Veneman Associates, San Francisco, California
1975-1976 Served as Counselor to Vice President Nelson Rockefeller, Washington, D.C.
1977- Vice President and Manager, Braun and Company, Washington, D.C.
1982 April 11 Died, Sacramento, California
Scope and Content of Collection
Correspondence, speeches, memoranda, reports, clippings, sound recordings, and photographs relating to domestic political issues in the United States, especially welfare and social policy, and to national and California state politics.
Ford, Gerald R., 1913-2006.; Nixon, Richard M. (Richard Milhous), 1913-1994.; Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich), 1908-1979.; United States. Dept. of Health, Education and Welfare.; California--Politics and government--1951-; Phonotapes.; Public welfare--United States.; United States--Politics and government--1969-1974.; United States--Politics and government--1974-1977.; United States--Politics and government.; United States--Social policy.
- BIOGRAPHICAL FILE, 1959-1978 (Boxes 1-6)
  Scope and Contents note
  Appointment books, business papers, certificates, financial records, guest list, interview, medical records, note books, passport application, printed matter, profile, receipt for papers, remarks about John Veneman, scrapbooks, telephone messages, travel records and miscellany, arranged alphabetically by physical form.
  - Appointment books, 1973-1977 (Box-folder 1: 1)
  - Business papers
    - General (Box-folder 1: 2)
    - Curriculum vitae (Box-folder 1: 3)
    - Financial records (Box-folder 1: 4)
    - Itinerary (Box-folder 1: 5)
    - Memoranda
      - Undated (Box-folder 1: 6)
      - 1973-1974 (Box-folder 1: 7-8)
      - 1977
        - January-August (Box-folder 1: 9-16)
        - September-December (Box-folder 2: 1-4)
      - 1978 (Box-folder 2: 5-14)
    - Minutes of meetings, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 2: 15-16)
    - Notes (Box-folder 2: 17)
    - Pamphlet (Box-folder 2: 18)
    - Press release (Box-folder 2: 19)
    - Proposals (Box-folder 2: 20)
    - Report (Box-folder 2: 21)
    - Telegram (Box-folder 2: 22)
    - Work plan (Box-folder 2: 23)
  - Certificates, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 2: 24)
  - Financial records, 1976 (Box-folder 2: 25)
  - Guest list (Box-folder 2: 26)
  - Interview, 1971 (Box-folder 2: 27)
  - Medical records (Box-folder 2: 28)
  - Note books, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 2: 29)
  - Passport application (Box-folder 3: 1)
  - Printed matter (Box-folder 3: 2)
  - Profile (Box-folder 3: 3)
  - Receipt for papers (Box-folder 3: 4)
  - Remarks about John G. Veneman by others (Box-folder 3: 5)
  - Scrapbooks
    - 1959-1962 (Box-folder 3: 6)
    - 1961-1962 (Box-folder 3: 7)
    - 1962 (Box-folder 3: 8)
    - 1963-1964 (Box-folder 4: 1-2)
    - 1965-1966 (Box-folder 5: 1-2)
    - 1967 (Box-folder 6: 1)
  - Telephone messages, 1976 (Box-folder 6: 2)
  - Travel records (Box-folder 6: 3)
  - Miscellany (Box-folder 6: 4)
- CORRESPONDENCE, 1969-1979 (Boxes 6-12)
  Letters arranged alphabetically by correspondent. Includes a few letters neither from nor to John Veneman.
  - General (Box-folder 6: 5)
  - Abernethy, Robert (Box-folder 6: 6)
  - Adam, Ray (Box-folder 6: 7)
  - Adams, Heather R. (Box-folder 6: 8)
  - Adams, Lee L. (Box-folder 6: 9)
  - Adams, Leland C. (Box-folder 6: 10)
  - Alexander, J. Saba (Box-folder 6: 11)
  - Allen, Howard P. (Box-folder 6: 12)
  - Allen, James (Box-folder 6: 13)
  - Allison, Richard (Box-folder 6: 14)
  - Amway Corporation (Box-folder 6: 15)
  - Anderson, Robert H. (Box-folder 6: 16)
  - Andrews, George (Box-folder 6: 17)
  - Armao, Robert F. (Box-folder 6: 18)
  - Arneson, Paul (Box-folder 6: 19)
  - Augsbury, Frank A., Jr. (Box-folder 6: 20)
  - Avard, Paul F. (Box-folder 6: 21)
  - Averett, Elliott (Box-folder 6: 22)
  - Bagley, William T., Mr. and Mrs. (Box-folder 6: 23)
  - Baker, James, III (Box-folder 6: 24)
  - Baker, Perren (Box-folder 6: 25)
  - Ball, Robert (Box-folder 6: 26)
  - Barrett, E. L. (Box-folder 6: 27)
  - Barth, Michael C. (Box-folder 6: 28)
  - Bateman, Raymond K. (Box-folder 6: 29)
  - Beatty, Colwell (Box-folder 6: 30)
  - Bedell, Catherine May (Box-folder 6: 31)
  - Bedrosian, John C. (Box-folder 6: 32)
  - Bennett, Berkeley V. (Box-folder 6: 33)
  - Bennett, Douglas P. (Box-folder 6: 34)
  - Berendt, Lee (Box-folder 6: 35)
  - Berstein, Bernice (Box-folder 6: 36)
  - Beverly, Robert G. (Box-folder 6: 37)
  - Billock, Sarah Massengale (Box-folder 6: 38)
  - Bishop, Jim (Box-folder 6: 39)
  - Blatchford, Joseph (Box-folder 6: 40)
  - Blendon, Robert (Box-folder 6: 41)
  - Board of Governors, Federal City Club (Box-folder 6: 42)
  - Bologna, Joseph (Box-folder 6: 43)
  - Bomberger, Bruce (Box-folder 6: 44)
  - Borland, Jack (Box-folder 6: 45)
  - Boyle, Audrey A. (Box-folder 6: 46)
  - Bradley, Thomas (Box-folder 6: 47)
  - Brady, Rodney H. (Box-folder 6: 48)
  - Brand, George (Box-folder 7: 1)
  - Braun, T. W. (Box-folder 7: 2)
  - Bretz, Charles G., Jr. (Box-folder 7: 3)
  - Brock, Bill (Box-folder 7: 4)
  - Brooks, Harry W., Jr. (Box-folder 7: 5)
  - Brousse, Robert J. (Box-folder 7: 6)
  - Brown, David S. J. (Box-folder 7: 7)
  - Brown, Edmund G., Jr. (Box-folder 7: 8)
  - Brown, Janet (Box-folder 7: 9)
  - Brown, Robert C. (Box-folder 7: 10)
  - Brunsdale, Anne (Box-folder 7: 11)
  - Bunje, Ralph B. (Box-folder 7: 12)
  - Burgener, Clair W. (Box-folder 7: 13)
  - Burke, Yvonne Braithwaite (Box-folder 7: 14)
  - Burney, David (Box-folder 7: 15)
  - Burns, Frank J., Jr. (Box-folder 7: 16)
  - Burns, Richard, Mr. and Mrs. (Box-folder 7: 17)
  - Burton, John L. (Box-folder 7: 18)
  - Burton, Phillip (Box-folder 7: 19)
  - Busby, Philip (Box-folder 7: 20)
  - Butler, Lewis H., Mr. and Mrs. (Box-folder 7: 21)
  - Butler, F. Patrick (Box-folder 7: 22)
  - Byers, Buckley M. (Box-folder 7: 23)
  - Bynum, Robert P. (Box-folder 7: 24)
  - Califano, Joseph A., Jr. (Box-folder 7: 25)
  - Campbell, Russell (Box-folder 7: 26)
  - Campbell, Selma (Box-folder 7: 27)
  - Campbell, W. Glenn (Box-folder 7: 28)
  - Cannon, James M., Mr. and Mrs. (Box-folder 7: 29)
  - Carlucci, Frank C. (Box-folder 7: 30)
  - Carn, Jake (Box-folder 7: 31)
  - Carey, Norval E. (Box-folder 7: 32)
  - Carter, David (Box-folder 7: 33)
  - Cavanaugh, James (Box-folder 7: 34)
  - Champion, Hale (Box-folder 7: 35)
  - Clark, Burland (Box-folder 7: 36)
  - Clark, Harry W. (Box-folder 7: 37)
  - Clarke, Stuart H. (Box-folder 7: 38)
  - Clausen, Don (Box-folder 7: 39)
  - Coffey, Bert (Box-folder 7: 40)
  - Coffey, Duncan M. (Box-folder 7: 41)
  - Cohen, Wilbur J. (Box-folder 7: 42)
  - Colby, William E. (Box-folder 7: 43)
  - Coldiron, Ashleigh (Box-folder 7: 44)
  - Coleman, William T., Jr. (Box-folder 7: 45)
  - Colness, Jerry L. (Box-folder 7: 46)
  - Compton, Harry (Box-folder 7: 47)
  - Cook, Marlow (Box-folder 7: 48)
  - Cook, Richard (Box-folder 7: 49)
  - Cooks, Stoney (Box-folder 7: 50)
  - Coop, Bob (Box-folder 7: 51)
  - Cordova, Jorge, Jr. (Box-folder 7: 52)
  - Corman, James C. (Box-folder 7: 53)
  - Cox, Derryck E. (Box-folder 7: 54)
  - Crist, Frank Lee, Jr. (Box-folder 7: 55)
  - Cranston, Alan (Box-folder 7: 56)
    Includes Cranston's letter to President Jimmy Carter.
  - Cross, Christopher T. (Box-folder 7: 57)
  - Cross, Travis (Box-folder 7: 58)
  - Curb, Michael (Box-folder 7: 59)
  - Curtis, Pamela G. (Box-folder 7: 60)
  - Damir, Robert M. (Box-folder 7: 61)
  - Danforth, Robert S. (Box-folder 7: 62)
  - Danielson, George E. (Box-folder 7: 63)
  - Davant, James W. (Box-folder 7: 64)
  - Davis, Charles O. (Box-folder 7: 65)
  - Davis, Hilton (Box-folder 7: 66)
  - Deaver, Michael K. (Box-folder 7: 67)
  - Del Monte Corporation (Alan Caldwell and Michael Roudnev) (Box-folder 7: 68)
  - Derzon, Robert A. (Box-folder 7: 69)
  - Deukmejian, George (Box-folder 7: 70)
  - Dewey, Ralph B. (Box-folder 7: 71)
  - Dickey, Charles D., Jr. (Box-folder 7: 72)
  - Dietel, William M. (Box-folder 7: 73)
  - District of Columbia (Box-folder 7: 74)
  - District of Columbia, Department of Transportation (Box-folder 7: 75)
  - Dixon, Howard (Box-folder 7: 76)
  - Doerr, David (Box-folder 7: 77)
  - Doherty, Mary K. (Box-folder 7: 78)
  - Dole, Hollis (Box-folder 7: 79)
  - Donaldson, William H. (Box-folder 7: 80)
  - Dowell, Emery B. (Box-folder 7: 81)
  - Dozier, William B. (Box-folder 7: 82)
  - Dubrowin, Raphael (Box-folder 7: 83)
  - Duffy, Edward W. (Box-folder 7: 84)
  - Duval, Merlin K. (Box-folder 7: 85)
  - Dwight, James S. (Box-folder 7: 86)
  - Dymally, Mervyn M. (Box-folder 7: 87)
  - Edwards, Max N. (Box-folder 7: 88)
  - Edwards, Richard A. (Box-folder 7: 89)
  - Eisenstadt, Ben (Box-folder 7: 90)
  - Eklund, Coy G. (Box-folder 7: 91)
  - Eli Lilly and Company (Richard W. Garrett, J. E. Koffenberger and William Murphy) (Box-folder 7: 92)
  - Elliott, Wright L. (Box-folder 8: 1)
  - Energy Management Services, Inc. (Box-folder 8: 2)
  - Englehart, E. (Box-folder 8: 3)
  - Eren, Nuri (Box-folder 8: 4)
  - Erickson, Robert J. (Box-folder 8: 5)
  - Erman, Herbert S. (Box-folder 8: 6)
  - Ewald, William R., Jr. (Box-folder 8: 7)
  - Fagin, David K. (Box-folder 8: 8)
  - Falk, James H. (Box-folder 8: 9)
  - Farkas, L. Peter (Box-folder 8: 10)
  - Fat, Wing (Box-folder 8: 11)
  - Fenninger, Leonard D. (Box-folder 8: 12)
  - Fernandez, Nino (Box-folder 8: 13)
  - Finch, Robert H. (Box-folder 8: 14)
    Includes letters written by Robert Finch to others.
  - Fisher, Lawrence W. (Box-folder 8: 15)
  - Fleming, Larry (Box-folder 8: 16)
  - Flournoy, Houston (Box-folder 8: 17)
  - Fomon, Robert H. (Box-folder 8: 18)
  - Ford, Edsel (Box-folder 8: 19)
  - Fore, Richard L. (Box-folder 8: 20)
  - Forward, Walter (Box-folder 8: 21)
  - Fraher, Donald E. (Box-folder 8: 22)
  - Francolini, Emilio (Box-folder 8: 23)
  - Fraser, Edie (Box-folder 8: 24)
  - French, Jayne T. (Box-folder 8: 25)
  - Frenzel, Bill (Box-folder 8: 26)
  - Friedman, Richard E. (Box-folder 8: 27)
  - Fulton, Wallace C. (Box-folder 8: 28)
  - Gabriel, John A. (Box-folder 8: 29)
  - Gardiner, Robert H. (Box-folder 8: 30)
  - Gardner, Geoffrey L. (Box-folder 8: 31)
  - Garibaldi, James D. (Box-folder 8: 32)
  - Gavin, Stephen D. (Box-folder 8: 33)
  - Gette, Robert L. (Box-folder 8: 34)
  - Gibson, Robert (Box-folder 8: 35)
  - Ginsberg, Mitchell I. (Box-folder 8: 36)
  - Glanville, James W. (Box-folder 8: 37)
  - Glenday, Ian (Box-folder 8: 38)
  - Goldberg, Larry (Box-folder 8: 39)
  - Goldman, Marvin (Box-folder 8: 40)
  - Goldman, Patricia (Box-folder 8: 41)
  - Gorman, Martha (Box-folder 8: 42)
  - Gradison, Willis D., Jr. (Box-folder 8: 43)
  - Grady, Stafford A. (Box-folder 8: 44)
  - Graeber, George (Box-folder 8: 45)
  - Grant, Gary W. (Box-folder 8: 46)
  - Grant, William W. (Box-folder 8: 47)
  - Graves, James (Box-folder 8: 48)
  - Gray, L. P., III (Box-folder 8: 49)
  - Grenier, William (Box-folder 8: 50)
  - Griffith, William (Box-folder 8: 51)
  - Grillo, Vincent R., Jr. (Box-folder 8: 52)
  - Gross, Joel H. (Box-folder 8: 53)
  - Gustafson, Robert H. (Box-folder 8: 54)
  - Hanrahan, Robert P. (Box-folder 8: 55)
  - Harper, John D. (Box-folder 8: 56)
  - Harris, Cynthia B. (Box-folder 8: 57)
  - Harris, Everette B. (Box-folder 8: 58)
  - Harris, Richard (Box-folder 8: 59)
  - Harrison, Joseph W. (Box-folder 8: 60)
  - Hartz, J. Ernest, Jr. (Box-folder 8: 61)
  - Hasenkamp, Bruce (Box-folder 8: 62)
  - Hass, Ewing (Box-folder 8: 63)
  - Hawkins, Paul M. (Box-folder 8: 64)
  - Hayward, Nancy S. (Box-folder 8: 65)
  - Hefter, Henry (Box-folder 8: 66)
  - Heinz, H. John, III (Box-folder 8: 67)
  - Helms, Jesse A. (Box-folder 8: 68)
  - Hemphill, Bernice M. (Box-folder 8: 69)
  - Henricksen, Don (Box-folder 8: 70)
  - Heron, Julian B., Jr. (Box-folder 8: 71)
  - Herringer, Fred (Box-folder 8: 72)
  - Herter, Christian A., Jr. (Box-folder 8: 73)
  - Herter, Susan (Box-folder 8: 74)
  - Hewitt, William A. (Box-folder 8: 75)
  - Hill, Richardson, Jr. (Box-folder 8: 76)
  - Hobbs, Claude E. (Box-folder 8: 77)
  - Hobbs, Lilian (Box-folder 8: 78)
  - Hohensee, Richard D. (Box-folder 8: 79)
  - Holland, James R. (Box-folder 8: 80)
  - Holmes, Peter (Box-folder 8: 81)
  - Holt, Barbara (Box-folder 8: 82)
  - Hooker, Roger W., Jr. (Box-folder 8: 83)
  - Hope, Judith Richard (Box-folder 9: 1)
  - Hoover, J. Edgar (Box-folder 9: 2)
  - Hudoba, Michael (Box-folder 9: 3)
  - Huldrum, Kathy (Box-folder 9: 4)
  - Hummel, Don (Box-folder 9: 5)
  - Humphreys, George W. (Box-folder 9: 6)
  - Hunter, Oakley (Box-folder 9: 7)
  - Iliine, Andre S. (Box-folder 9: 8)
  - Jenckes, Joseph (Box-folder 9: 9)
  - Jerecki, Henry G. (Box-folder 9: 10)
  - Joe, Barbara (Box-folder 9: 11)
  - Johnson, Peter (Box-folder 9: 12)
  - Johnson, Raty (Box-folder 9: 13)
  - June, Eva (Box-folder 9: 14)
  - Kadick, Misha (Box-folder 9: 15)
  - Kahl, B. Michael (Box-folder 9: 16)
  - Kalmbach, Herb (Box-folder 9: 17)
  - Kaye, Peter (Box-folder 9: 18)
  - Kehoe, John T. (Box-folder 9: 19)
  - Kelly, Richard (Box-folder 9: 20)
  - Kelser, George (Box-folder 9: 21)
  - Kemp, Jack (Box-folder 9: 22)
  - Kennedy, Art (Box-folder 9: 23)
  - Ketchum, William M. (Box-folder 9: 24)
  - Kilberg, Bobbie (Box-folder 9: 25)
  - King, Colbert I. (Box-folder 9: 26)
  - Kirby, Robert E. (Box-folder 9: 27)
  - Kirklin, John W. (Box-folder 9: 28)
  - Kirkman, Walter B. (Box-folder 9: 29)
  - Kirkwood, Robert (Box-folder 9: 30)
  - Kline, Frank C. (Box-folder 9: 31)
  - Knauer, Virginia H. (Box-folder 9: 32)
  - Knebel, John A. (Box-folder 9: 33)
  - Knowles, John (Box-folder 9: 34)
  - Knox, John T. (Box-folder 9: 35)
  - Kolberg, William H. (Box-folder 9: 36)
  - Kolbye, Albert C., Jr. (Box-folder 9: 37)
  - Konynenburg, Dirk Van, Mr. and Mrs. (Box-folder 9: 38)
  - Kornegay, Horace R. (Box-folder 9: 39)
  - Kraft, Timothy E. (Box-folder 9: 40)
  - Kuchel, Thomas H. (Box-folder 9: 41)
  - Lacey, Michael J. (Box-folder 9: 42)
  - Ladd, Bruce C., Jr. (Box-folder 9: 43)
  - Laird, Tim (Box-folder 9: 44)
  - Lamb, Joan E. (Box-folder 9: 45)
  - Langford, Ellis C. (Box-folder 9: 46)
  - Lannon, E. R. (Box-folder 9: 47)
  - Leo, Charles G. (Box-folder 9: 48)
  - Levine, Robert H. (Box-folder 9: 49)
  - Lewin, Larry (Box-folder 9: 50)
  - Lewis, Jerry (Box-folder 9: 51)
  - Lewitt, Maurice (Box-folder 9: 52)
  - Liebenson, Herbert (Box-folder 9: 53)
  - Lieberth, Charlie (Box-folder 9: 54)
  - Lindsey, J. B. (Box-folder 9: 55)
  - Lloyd, Jim (Box-folder 9: 56)
  - Lugar, Richard G. (Box-folder 9: 57)
  - Luhrs, Caro E. (Box-folder 9: 58)
  - Luther, Patty (Box-folder 9: 59)
  - Lyng, Richard, Mr. and Mrs. (Box-folder 9: 60)
  - M-K Rescue Squad (Box-folder 9: 61)
  - McCarthy, Leo T. (Box-folder 9: 62)
  - McCloskey, Paul (Box-folder 9: 63)
  - McDonald, Michael L. (Box-folder 9: 64)
  - McDonough, Mamie (Box-folder 9: 65)
  - McFall, John J. (Box-folder 9: 66)
  - McFarland, Richard M. (Box-folder 9: 67)
  - McGregor, Clark (Box-folder 9: 68)
  - McKinney, Stewart B. (Box-folder 9: 69)
  - McLane, James W. (Box-folder 9: 70)
  - McNamara, Robert S. (Box-folder 9: 71)
  - McWalter, Keith (Box-folder 9: 72)
  - Mack, Tom (Box-folder 9: 73)
  - Malatesta, Thomas (Box-folder 9: 74)
  - Malek, Frederick V. (Box-folder 9: 75)
  - Marck, C. T. (Box-folder 9: 76)
  - Margolis, Larry (Box-folder 9: 77)
  - Marron, Donald B. (Box-folder 9: 78)
  - Marsh, John O., Jr. (Box-folder 9: 79)
  - Marshall, Gary (Box-folder 9: 80)
  - Marshall, Larry (Box-folder 9: 81)
  - Martin, James R. (Box-folder 9: 82)
  - Martin, John H. (Box-folder 9: 83)
  - Marumoto, William H. (Box-folder 9: 84)
  - Masso, Anthony R. (Box-folder 9: 85)
  - Mastrangelo, Richard (Box-folder 9: 86)
  - Mastrangelo, Tally P. (Box-folder 9: 87)
  - Mathews, David (Box-folder 9: 88)
  - Matte, Harry (Box-folder 9: 89)
  - Means, Grady E. (Box-folder 9: 90)
  - Medley, Kenneth W. (Box-folder 9: 91)
  - Melamed, Leo (Box-folder 9: 92)
  - Menges, Constantine (Box-folder 9: 93)
  - Meschery, Ann (Box-folder 9: 94)
  - Metz, Douglas W. (Box-folder 9: 95)
  - Meyer, James H. (Box-folder 9: 96)
  - Miles, Rufus E., Jr. (Box-folder 9: 97)
  - Miller, Clifford (Box-folder 9: 98)
  - Miller, John J. (Box-folder 9: 99)
  - Milton, John (Box-folder 9: 100)
  - Minger, Walter W. (Box-folder 9: 101)
  - Monagan, Robert, Mr. and Mrs. (Box-folder 10: 1)
  - Moon, John E. (Box-folder 10: 2)
  - Moore, George C. J. (Box-folder 10: 3)
  - Morgenthaler, David T. (Box-folder 10: 4)
  - Morrill, William A. (Box-folder 10: 5)
  - Mosconi, George, Mrs. (Box-folder 10: 6)
  - Moskow, Michael H. (Box-folder 10: 7)
  - Motley, Tony (Box-folder 10: 8)
  - Mrak, Emil M. (Box-folder 10: 9)
  - Mulligan, Raymond J. (Box-folder 10: 10)
  - Murphy, Frank, Jr. (Box-folder 10: 11)
  - Murphy, Richard W. (Box-folder 10: 12)
  - Nagle, Robert O. (Box-folder 10: 13)
  - Nakano, Patty (Box-folder 10: 14)
  - National Center for Health Services Research (Box-folder 10: 15)
  - Newman, Frank (Box-folder 10: 16)
  - Newman, Richard J. (Box-folder 10: 17)
  - Newman, Theodore, Mr. and Mrs. (Box-folder 10: 18)
  - Newmyer, Arthur, III (Box-folder 10: 19)
  - Nishi, Martha (Box-folder 10: 20)
  - Novak, Robert (Box-folder 10: 21)
  - Nystrom, Karin (Box-folder 10: 22)
  - O'Brien, Daniel F. (Box-folder 10: 23)
  - O'Connell, Robert B. (Box-folder 10: 24)
  - Offen, Neil H. (Box-folder 10: 25)
  - Okano, Mitsutake (Box-folder 10: 26)
  - O'Keefe, Charles (Box-folder 10: 27)
  - Olsen, Van (Box-folder 10: 28)
  - Olson, Andrew H. (Box-folder 10: 29)
  - Olson, Diane (Box-folder 10: 30)
  - O'Malley, John (Box-folder 10: 31)
  - O'Neill, Paul (Box-folder 10: 32)
  - O'Neill, Rodney (Box-folder 10: 33)
  - O'Neill, William, Mr. and Mrs. (Box-folder 10: 34)
  - Osborn, Barbara (Box-folder 10: 35)
  - Osius, Catherine (Box-folder 10: 36)
  - Osius, Elsbeth K. (Box-folder 10: 37)
  - Ostronic, Frank (Box-folder 10: 38)
  - Overman, Dean L., Mr. and Mrs. (Box-folder 10: 39)
  - Overs, Harry (Box-folder 10: 40)
  - Packwood, Bob (Box-folder 10: 41)
  - Paine, Merlin M. (Box-folder 10: 42)
  - Panetta, Leon E. (Box-folder 10: 43)
  - Parham, William F. (Box-folder 10: 44)
  - Perry, Robert H. (Box-folder 10: 45)
  - Peterson, Russell W. (Box-folder 10: 46)
  - Phillips, Harry A., Jr. (Box-folder 10: 47)
  - Pierno, Anthony R. (Box-folder 10: 48)
  - Pilliod, Charles J., Jr. (Box-folder 10: 49)
  - Pittenger, Richard (Box-folder 10: 50)
  - Pope, Raymond (Box-folder 10: 51)
  - Post, John (Box-folder 10: 52)
  - Pottinger, J. Stanley (Box-folder 10: 53)
  - Pownall, Thomas (Box-folder 10: 54)
  - Prager, Susan Westerberg (Box-folder 10: 55)
  - Prine, Art (Box-folder 10: 56)
  - Quern, Arthur F. (Box-folder 10: 57)
  - Quinn, Donald (Box-folder 10: 58)
  - Quinn, Joseph R. (Box-folder 10: 59)
  - Quinn, Richard M. (Box-folder 10: 60)
  - Rainbolt, John V., II (Box-folder 10: 61)
  - Rashman, Richard M. (Box-folder 10: 62)
  - Ratcliff, Richard E. (Box-folder 10: 63)
  - Raye, Vance (Box-folder 10: 64)
  - Reagan, Ronald (Box-folder 10: 65)
  - Rees, Thomas M. (Box-folder 10: 66)
  - Reutershan, Thomas P. (Box-folder 10: 67)
  - Reynolds, Nancy Clark (Box-folder 10: 68)
  - Rhodes, John (Box-folder 10: 69)
  - Rice, Joseph A. (Box-folder 10: 70)
  - Richardson, Elliot L. (Box-folder 10: 71)
  - Riefkohl, Otto J., II (Box-folder 10: 72)
  - Rivet, Ralph (Box-folder 10: 73)
  - Roberts, Charles R. (Box-folder 10: 74)
  - Robinson, Lawrence J., Jr. (Box-folder 10: 75)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Box-folder 10: 76)
  - Rogers, Jim (Box-folder 10: 77)
  - Rogers, Paul G. (Box-folder 10: 78)
  - Rogers, William P. (Box-folder 10: 79)
  - Rohatyn, Felix G. (Box-folder 10: 80)
  - Rood, Rodney (Box-folder 10: 81)
  - Rosenbaum, Richard M. (Box-folder 10: 82)
  - Rosenberg, Laurence M. (Box-folder 10: 83)
  - Roth, Barry N. (Box-folder 10: 84)
  - Roy, William R. (Box-folder 11: 1)
  - Rumsfeld, Donald H. (Box-folder 11: 2)
  - Ryan, Leo J. (Box-folder 11: 3)
  - Salzman, Jerrold E. (Box-folder 11: 4)
  - Sample, Frank, Mr. and Mrs. (Box-folder 11: 5)
  - Samuels, Frank E., Jr. (Box-folder 11: 6)
  - Scales, John K. (Box-folder 11: 7)
  - Seely, Richard (Box-folder 11: 8)
  - Schenk, Lynn (Box-folder 11: 9)
  - Schiff, John M. (Box-folder 11: 10)
  - Schmidt, Robert L. (Box-folder 11: 11)
  - Scott, Hugh (Box-folder 11: 12)
  - Seawell, William T. (Box-folder 11: 13)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission (Box-folder 11: 14)
  - Seidman, L. William (Box-folder 11: 15)
  - Seitel, Fraser P. (Box-folder 11: 16)
  - Selig, Robert W. (Box-folder 11: 17)
  - Seubold, Frank H. (Box-folder 11: 18)
  - Shaffer, Jack A. (Box-folder 11: 19)
  - Shastid, Jon B. (Box-folder 11: 20)
  - Shian, George L. (Box-folder 11: 21)
  - Shinn, Richard R. (Box-folder 11: 22)
  - Shubert, Gustave H. (Box-folder 11: 23)
  - Shutt, James W. (Box-folder 11: 24)
  - Siciliano, Rocco C. (Box-folder 11: 25)
  - Simon, D. Alexander (Box-folder 11: 26)
  - Simon, David (Box-folder 11: 27)
  - Simon, Lucinda (Box-folder 11: 28)
  - Simmons, William (Box-folder 11: 29)
  - Singer, Thomas K. (Box-folder 11: 30)
  - Smalley, Robert M. (Box-folder 11: 31)
  - Smith, James H. (Box-folder 11: 32)
  - Smith, Thym S. (Box-folder 11: 33)
  - Sobel, Stanton L. (Box-folder 11: 34)
  - Sonneborn, Charles B. (Box-folder 11: 35)
  - Spear, William W., Mr. and Mrs. (Box-folder 11: 36)
  - Speer, Edgar B. (Box-folder 11: 37)
  - Spierling, John (Box-folder 11: 38)
  - Spina, Al (Box-folder 11: 39)
  - Splane, Beverly (Box-folder 11: 40)
  - Sprague, Dan (Box-folder 11: 41)
  - Stanton, J. William (Box-folder 11: 42)
  - Stembler, John H., Jr. (Box-folder 11: 43)
  - Stowell, Christopher E. (Box-folder 11: 44)
  - Strelow, Roger (Box-folder 11: 45)
  - Stuart, Constance (Box-folder 11: 46)
  - Taft, William H., IV (Box-folder 11: 47)
  - Taylor, Waller, II (Box-folder 11: 48)
  - Ternes, Joseph J. (Box-folder 11: 49)